

Mohammad Yoddi Dahsyat

Full Stack Developer

I am 24 years old, currently live in Purbalingga, Central Java, Indonesia. I am a full stack web developer with great problem solving skills and a good sense of design. I have more than 1 year of experience working as a fullstack and frontend developer.

Skills

Coding Languages:

- Javascript
- HTML
- CSS / SCSS
- PHP
- MySQL
- PostgreSQL

Frameworks/Libraries:

- ReactJs
- NodeJs
- ExpressJs
- jQuery
- AJAX
- Codelgniter
- Bootstrap
- React Native

Others:

- Git
- Photoshop
- Illustrator
- Figma

Contact

+6285157667536 yoddi.dahsyat@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/yoddidahsyat

Visit my portfolio site: yoddidahsyat.netlify.app

Work Experience

uHoo Pte., Ltd.

Web developer (frontend)

Oct 2021 - Aug 2022 | Singapore, Full Time Remote

 Maintain frontend web development for premium and partner dashboard to show visualized data using ReactJs

PT. Talenta Indonesia Raya

Full stack developer

Feb 2021 - Aug 2021 | Jakarta, Hybrid (WFH and WFO)

- Develop and maintain online psycho-test website application and server to be used by thousands of users concurrently using PHP, mySQL, jQuery, and Google Cloud Platform.
- Create new assessment kits and modules to be used by clients.

The Ministry of Communication and Information of Indonesia (Kemkominfo) Internship

Mar 2020 - May 2020 | Jakarta

• Create a web app for employee management system using PHP and mySQL.

Education

Formal

Jenderal Soedirman University

Electrical Engineering

2016 - Present

- Focus on Information System and the Internet of Things.
- Passed the funding phase of the Student Creativity Program (PKM) in the IoT field.
- Willing to graduate in early 2023

Training/Course

Dumbways.id

Full Stack Developer bootcamp

Dec 2020 - Jan 2021

- Learn about full stack programming using NodeJs, ReactJs, and React Native
- Build two web apps and one mobile app within a month

SkillAcademy.com

Basic Foundation for Data Science

Oct 2020

Learn basic data processing with python and mysql

Organization

LavakBahagia.id

Media and Publication Staff

Dec 2020

Alliance of Electrical Engineering Laboratory

Lab Assistance and Coordinator

Feb 2020 - Jul 2020